Ambuj Dubey (Full Stack Developer)

ambujdubey89@gmail.com (+91) 9753750955 www.linkedin.com/in/ambuj-dubey-2923b456 https://github.com/ambujbpl Address :- CM-78 Indore

Summary of Qualifications

Dedicated and efficient full stack developer with 4.3+ years experience in the application layers, presentation layers, and databases. Played major role with high-level proficiency in the following technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, SQL, MongoDB, Angular JS and React JS. I am very familiar and experienced with Web Application Architecture, have worked with a good number of successful development teams and provide the ability to work by taking complete ownership of tasks.

Work Experience

Full-Stack Developer (July 2019 to present)

Logikview Analytics, MPSEDC IT Park Electronics Complex, Indore. 452010

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Collaborates with development team which includes Product Manager, Software Engineer and Quality Assurance team to identifying software problems, testing methods, and best solutions.
- Developed full-stack applications which processed, analyzed, and rendered data visually.
- Integrated app-based solutions with databases, file systems, and cloud-based systems.
- Object-Oriented Analysis.

Junior Full Stack Developer (June 2018-June 2019)

Ideata Analytics, MPSEDC IT Park Electronics Complex, Indore. 452010

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Developed software applications with technologies like Nodejs, Strapi, Express.js and integration with REST APIs for ADFS services, live tracking application and other services.
- Managed, optimized, and updated databases as necessary.
- Collaborates with development team and create testing methods.
- Object-Oriented Analysis and Relational Database Systems.
- Testing the designed unit test case.

Software Developer (November 2017 - May 2018)

Green Ticks Bhopal 462026

Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Developed full-stack applications which processed, analyzed, and rendered data visually with technologies like Nodejs, Express.js Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap3.
- Studied, evaluated, and proposed solutions to complex architectural challenges for the purpose of introducing new features.

Software Engineer (October 2016 - October 2017)

Mobigesture Software Pvt. Ltd. Banjara Hills,

Hyderabad Key Qualifications & Responsibilities

- Developed app-solutions using a variety of languages, frameworks, and platforms such as Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap3 SQL, and HTML.
- UI-Design and Development of Source code.
- Responsive Web Design (Bootstrap framework).

Key Skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, PHP.
- Bootstrap, Materilized and Bulma CSS
- Node JS, Express, EJS viewer
- Angular IS
- React Native, Expo
- React JS
- MySql
- SQL Server Databases
- MongoDB

Academic Qualification

P G Diploma	C-DAC Hyderabad 2016 batch
M. Tech	Digital Communication RGPV Bhopal 2015
B.Tech	Electronics & Telecommunication RGPV Bhopal 2011
12 th	Mathematics M.P. Board 2007
10 th	M.P. Board 2005

Personal Profile

Father's Name	Mr. Shravan Dubey
Mother's Name	Mrs. Kalpana Dubey
Date of Birth	06-08-1989
Nationality	Indian
Languages Known	English, Hindi
Hobbies	Internet Surfing and sports activities.
Permanent Address	20-A Sachchidanand Nagar, BHEL, Bhopal (M.P.)
Skills and Proficiencies	Creative, Team Work, Willingness To Learn

Declaration

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Place: Indore (M.P.)

Date: (Ambuj Dubey)